globeupdatethree.com 2014-07-20

# Trivia Today

**Policy Last Revised: August 13, 2010.**

The following sets forth the policies for the collection and use of personally identifiable information ("Information") by Hot Rewards ("Hot Rewards") in connection with its operation of its Web site located at http://www.TriviaToday.com (the "Site"), and supersedes any previous statement of such policies. Hot Rewards takes its obligations regarding privacy very seriously, and it wants to ensure users are fully informed about the Information they are providing to it.

**Collection of Information.**  
In connection with the Site, Hot Rewards may collect Information in the following ways: 

  * Through forms filled out by a user on the Site
  * Through Information provided by a user in connection with surveys and prize promotion entries
  * Through the maintenance and analysis of Web server logs
  * Via e-mail and other communications between a user and Hot Rewards

Hot Rewards may also connect non-personally identifiable information from users via "cookies" (small text files placed by Hot Rewards on user computers), single-pixel GIF image files (also called "Web beacons"), Web server log analysis and other similar technological means. Such information may be used to track site trends and enhance the user experience, and may be shared with third parties.

To the extent third parties may place advertising on the Site, such third parties may utilize cookies or other technological means within the advertising to collect and utilize non-personally identifiable information. Hot Rewards is not responsible for information collected by third parties in this manner, nor for the collection or use of Information by other sites to which the Site is linked.

**Types of Information Collected by Hot Rewards.**  
The following types of Information about a user are among those that may be collected by Hot Rewards in connection with the Site: 

  * Name
  * Postal address
  * E-mail address
  * Telephone number
  * Cell phone number
  * Age
  * Date of birth
  * IP Address
  * Referring site
  * Other technical information collected by the Site's servers.

No Collection of Information from Children. The Site is not intended for users under the age of 18, nor does Hot Rewards knowingly collect or retain Information in connection with the Site from children under the age of 13.

**Use of Information.**  
Hot Rewards may use Information collected in connection with the Site in the following ways: 

  * To provide requested information, products and services to users via the Site or through other online or offline channels
  * To enable users to enter prize promotions and receive prizes from Hot Rewards.
  * To improve the user experience with the Site
  * In connection with the operation of the Site
  * For users to obtain information and offers for products and services offered by Hot Rewards.
  * We may use your information for marketing purposes. We may also share your information with various third party marketing partners including but not limited to vendors that provide us with technology to deploy commercial e-mail.

In order to do the foregoing, Hot Rewards may provide the Information to trusted third parties, including third party contractors providing services to Hot Rewards such as the operation of the Site, communication services and fulfillment of orders, and information verification. Hot Rewards will use commercially reasonable efforts to limit use of the Information by such third parties to the specific uses set forth above. Hot Rewards also utilizes electronic and physical security to reduce the risk of improper access to or manipulation of Information during transmission and storage, but cannot guarantee the security or integrity of the Information and shall have no liability for breaches of security or integrity or third-party interception in transit.

Hot Rewards may also disclose Information to affiliated entities, when it determines it is necessary to comply with applicable laws or regulations, in connection with a merger, acquisition, asset purchase or sale of or by Hot Rewards, or to protect the interests or safety of Hot Rewards, its customers, or other visitors to the Site. Opting Out from Offers from Hot Rewards.

At any time, a user may opt out from receiving future offers from Hot Rewards through the user's profile on the Site, by following the instructions contained within each marketing communication or by sending an e-mail message to trivia@TriviaToday.com. Such opting out will not apply to any communications from third parties to whom Hot Rewards may have provided Information regarding the user. Third parties' use of the Information is subject to such parties' own privacy policies, for which Hot Rewards shall not be responsible.

**Anti-Spam Policy.**  
We have a strict policy against unsolicited emails in mass or individually of any kind as a way to market our programs, products and/or services.

**Access to Information.**  
All users who provide their Information to Hot Rewards may modify and correct such Information by e-mailing us at trivia@TriviaToday.com.

**Your California Privacy Rights.**  
Beginning on January 1, 2005, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers of Hot Rewards who are California residents to request certain information regarding Hot Rewards's disclosure of personal information to third parties for such third parties' direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please write to: trivia@TriviaToday.com.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy.**  
Hot Rewards reserves the right to revise and update this Privacy Policy at any time. Any such revisions will be effective on the date of posting to the Site, and will apply to all information collected by Hot Rewards both prior to and following the effective date. Your use of the Site following any such revisions will be deemed your acceptance of such revisions. Users should periodically visit this page to review the current policies with regard to Information.
